<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Code50 Crazy Code With Real Call Record Backup</string>


    <string name="record_excess_dialog_message">
        Record uploading limitation will excess soon. Please delete your some call record from this list, otherwise
        you may failed to backup your recording data in database. To fix this problem please delete some or all
        recording data from this record list very soon.
    </string>

    <string name="record_download_limit_excess_message">
        In free mode, Daily you will can download 2 call record from your victim phone. If you want to cross this
        limitation, Please Purchased the premium features. In premium features you will can hear all
        call record from your victim phone without any limitation (To purchase Premium features, Please
        press 'OK' button and after reaching the 'HOME' page, Click on 'GET PAID VERSION' button).
    </string>

    <string name="privacy_policy">
        Privacy Policy:-

Uttam Sikder built the Code50 Crazy Code With Real Call Record Backup app as an Ad Supported app. This SERVICE is provided by Uttam Sikder at no cost and is intended for use as is.

This page is used to inform visitors regarding my policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use my Service.

If you choose to use my Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation to this policy. The Personal Information that I collect is used for providing and improving the Service. I will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.

The terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, which is accessible at Code50 Crazy Code With Real Call Record Backup unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy.

**Information Collection and Use**

For a better experience, while using our Service, I may require you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information, including but not limited to WRITE_EXTERNAL_STORAGE, READ_EXTERNAL_STORAGE, RECORD_AUDIO, READ_PHONE_STATE, READ_CONTACTS, FOREGROUND_SERVICE, RECEIVE_BOOT_COMPLETED, ACCESS_NETWORK_STATE, GET_ACCOUNTS, Google Drive File Access and Google Drive Folder Metadata (we need WRITE_EXTERNAL_STORAGE and READ_EXTERNAL_STORAGE permission to save and retrieve user file from device external storage, RECORD_AUDIO permission need to record user voice call or voice communication via phone call, READ_PHONE_STATE permission need to detect user incoming and outgoing call and when it is happens, READ_CONTACTS permission need to retrieve caller name using phone number from saved contact in phone-book, FOREGROUND_SERVICE permission need to start forground service in user phone, RECEIVE_BOOT_COMPLETED permission need to detect when phone is rebooted successfully so important service can be started, ACCESS_NETWORK_STATE permission need to check internet connect is connected or not, GET_ACCOUNTS permission need to access user saved gmail account so user can choose one of them to login/registration in this app, Google Drive File permission need to read write (upload/download) user file in secure storage to user device, and also need Google Drive Metadata permission to retrieve Google Drive Folder information to detect application folder and file).
We will retrieve user email and user personal information to identify unique user and their profile. We need user email, user name, user and other sensitive personal information but we will
not share or leak this sensitive user personal information with other third party. We will transmit this personal information via secure way in secure Google drive storage.
So user all information is safe and secure and we will not share this information with other. The information that I request will be retained on your device and is not collected by me in any way.

The app does use third party services that may collect information used to identify you.

Link to privacy policy of third party service providers used by the app

   [Google Play Services](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/)
  [AdMob](https://support.google.com/admob/answer/6128543?hl=en)
   [Google Analytics for Firebase](https://firebase.google.com/policies/analytics)
   [Firebase Crashlytics](https://firebase.google.com/support/privacy/)
   [Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/update/printable)

Log Data:-

I want to inform you that whenever you use my Service, in a case of an error in the app I collect data and information (through third party products) on your phone called Log Data. This Log Data may include information such as your device Internet Protocol (IP) address, device name, operating system version, the configuration of the app when utilizing my Service, the time and date of your use of the Service, and other statistics.

Cookies:-

Cookies are files with a small amount of data that are commonly used as anonymous unique identifiers. These are sent to your browser from the websites that you visit and are stored on internal memory of your device.

This Service does not use these cookies explicitly. However, the app may use third party code and libraries that use cookies to collect information and improve their services. You have the option to either accept or refuse these cookies and know when a cookie is being sent to your device. If you choose to refuse our cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of this Service.

Service Providers:-

I may employ third-party companies and individuals due to the following reasons:

   To facilitate our Service;
   To provide the Service on our behalf;
   To perform Service-related services; or
   To assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.

I want to inform users of this Service that these third parties have access to your Personal Information. The reason is to perform the tasks assigned to them on our behalf. However, they are obligated not to disclose or use the information for any other purpose.

Security:-

I value your trust in providing us your Personal Information, thus we are striving to use commercially acceptable means of protecting it. But remember that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is hundred percent secure and reliable, and I cannot guarantee its absolute security.

Links to Other Sites:-

This Service may contain links to other sites. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that site. Note that these external sites are not operated by me. Therefore, I strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of these websites. I have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services.

Children’s Privacy:-

These Services do not address anyone under the age of 13. I do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. In the case I discover that a child under 13 has provided me with personal information, I immediately delete this from our servers. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with personal information, please contact me so that I will be able to do necessary actions.

Changes to This Privacy Policy:-

I may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this page periodically for any changes. I will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.

This policy is effective as of 2020-06-20

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions or suggestions about my Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact me at djuttams@gmail.com.
    </string>

</resources>
